Guide to the American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA), New York Local Records WAG.282
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA), New York Local Office Records
1948-1993
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
American Federation of Television and Radio Artists
WAG.282
99 Linear Feet in 98 record cartons and 1 oversize flat box
The American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA), founded in 1952, is a union of approximately 70,000 members representing professional actors, journalists, dancers, singers, announcers, hosts, comedians, and disc jockeys from numerous media industries, including television, radio, cable, sound recordings, video productions, commercials, audio books, non-broadcast industrials, interactive games, internet productions, and other digital media. The union traces its origins to the 1937 founding of the American Federation of Radio Artists (AFRA) with 400 members and locals in New York and Los Angeles. In 2012, after numerous attempts, AFTRA and the Screen Actors Guild (SAG) successfully merged to form SAG-AFTRA. This guide describes the records of AFTRA's New York Local office from its founding through 1990. The collection consists of photographs, memoranda, correspondence, meeting minutes, financial records, formal agreements, recorded negotiations, constitutions and by-laws, and legal files documenting claims and arbitrations. The materials document the union's daily operations and governance, in addition to broader labor and social issues through the lens of entertainers and performers, including civil rights, anti-communism investigations, and workers' rights and protections. The collection also includes materials documenting the union's relationships and interactions with related domestic and international guilds and federations for performers.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Related Archival Materials
Actors' Equity Association Records (WAG 011)
Associated Actors and Artistes of America Records (WAG 110)
American Guild of Musical Artists Records (WAG 209)
American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA) National Office Records (WAG 281)
Separated Materials
Stand-By! newsletters were separated to the library serials collection.
Immediate Source of Acquisition Note
Donated by the American Federation of Television and Radio Artists in 2010. The accession number associated with this gift is 2008.047.
Historical/Biographical Note
The American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA) New York Local, founded in 1952, is AFTRA's union branch serving the interests of its members living and working in the greater New York City area, including professional actors, journalists, dancers, singers, announcers, hosts, comedians, and disc jockeys from numerous media industries, including television, radio, cable, sound recordings, video productions, commercials, audio books, non-broadcast industrials, interactive games, internet productions, and other digital media.
The history of AFTRA's New York Local is tied very closely to that of the national organization. It, along with Los Angeles, was the first local chapter established by the union's precursor (the American Federation of Radio Artists [AFRA]) and the national headquarters is also located in the city. The New York Local observes and advocates for its members' wages and working conditions by negotiating local contracts, recruiting members, educating its members on their rights, investigating grievances, filing legal claims, and inspecting working conditions through field representatives.
New York's historical prominence within the entertainment industry, including the production of radio, television, journalistic, and soap opera programming, have made it one of the largest and most active local chapters within the larger AFTRA union. The history of the local is a reflection of the history and progression of the entertainment industry. The local represents and advocates for members working for national networks and productions that happen to be based in the New York area (such as NBC or "All My Children"), as well as those involved in local productions or network affiliates (such as WNYC or performances from the New York Shakespeare Festival). Many prominent Manhattan-based comedians from the mid-20th century, including Sid Caesar, Mel Brooks, and Carl Reiner, joined and were represented by the New York AFTRA local as they became television performers. The local's legal representatives and field investigators administered numerous negotiations, claims, and on-set visits for the heavy level of daytime programming production taking place in the city, including talk shows and soap operas. The city's large media market, including broadcast news, local news media, and non-commercial educational media, contribute to the local's many members holding positions as announcers, hosts, newscasters, journalists, and disc jockeys.
The mid-20th century entertainment industry blacklist (also referred to as the Hollywood blacklist) that denied entertainment professionals employment based on their political beliefs or associations, real or suspected, created strife and dissent within AFTRA. The New York Local was especially vocal over the issue; their motions were sent to a national vote, but all failed. In 1955, the union passed a national referendum stating that any member who refused to cooperate with any government committee investigating alleged disloyalty or subversive activities "shall be subject to the charge that he is guilty of conduct prejudicial to the welfare of AFTRA" and may be "fined, censured, or expelled from the union by the member's local." In October 1997, AFTRA formally apologized for this position.
Major figures in the governance of AFTRA New York include Presidents Mark Smith (1938-1939), Alex McKee (1940), William P. Adams (1941-1944), House Jameson (1945), Clayton "Bud" Collyer (1946-1947), Nelson Case (1948-1949), Alan Bunce (1950-1951), Vinton Hayworth (1952-1954), Travis Johnson (1955), Charles Collingwood (1956), Luis van Rooten (1957), Virginia Payne (1958-1959), Bernard Lenrow (1960), Cliff Norton (1961-1962), Leon Janney (1963), Gene Rayburn (1964), Rex Marshall (1965), Carol Reed (1966), Mel Brandt (1966-1967), Kenneth Roberts (1968-1969), Kenneth Harvey (1970-1972), Jackson Beck (1973-1976), Martha Greenhouse (1977-1981), and Ann Loring (1982). Prominent former Executive Secretaries of the New York Local include George Heller (1937-1949), Kenneth Groot (1950-1952, 1955-1983), A. Frank Reel (1952-1953), Alex McKee (1953-1955), Reginald Dowell (1983-1986), Kim Roberts (1986-1987), and Helayne Antler (1987).
For more information on AFTRA's national history, please see: Guide to the American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA) National Office Records (WAG 281)
Sources:
Stand By!, July/August 1987. American Federation of Television and Radio Artists (AFTRA), New York Local Records; WAG 282; Box 17; Folder 2; Tamiment Library/Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives, New York University
http://www.sagaftra.org/history/aftra-history/aftra-history
Scope and Content Note
The records of the New York Local Office of American Federation of Television and Radio Artists cover the period from its founding as a radio-only union in 1937, through the addition of television to its jurisdiction in 1952, up to 1990. This collection consists of meeting minutes, constitutions, by-laws, contracts, correspondence, handbooks, newsletters, written agreements, financial statements, programs and records of the union's annual convention, and legal files documenting cases involving members' rights, benefits, and protections. The records also include materials documenting the New York union's relationships and interactions with related domestic (including other AFTRA locals) and international guilds and federations for performers.
The collection documents many of AFTRA's claims, negotiations, and investigations on behalf of its New York members, including those concerning pension, insurance, welfare claims, wrongful termination, protections for freelancers, contract violations, insufficient compensation, grievance procedures, on-set safety, and violations of collective bargaining rights. Members include performers working for national networks and productions that happen to be based in the New York area (such as NBC or "All My Children"), as well as those involved in local productions or network affiliates (such as WNYC or performances from the New York Shakespeare Festival). Particularly well represented in this collection are cases against the Inner City Broadcasting Corporation and Tuesday Productions, as well as charges resulting from the 1981 National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians (NABET) strike.
Because of New York's historical prominence within the entertainment industry, the history of the local is a reflection of the history and progression of labor within the entertainment industry. The materials document the union's daily operations and governance, in addition to broader labor and social issues through the lens of entertainers and performers, including civil rights, anti-communism investigations, and workers' rights and protections.
Arrangement
The collection consists of eight series:
I: Minutes
II: Constitutions, By-Laws, Agreements, Codes and Contracts
III: Administrative Files
IV: Conventions
V: Charges, Claims, and Arbitrations
VI: Negotiations
VII: Other Unions/Guilds/Federations
VIII Photographs: Unprocessed.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu, (212) 998-2630 with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Radio broadcasting |x Employees |x Labor unions |z United States.; Blacklisting of entertainers.; Actresses -- United States.; Actors -- United States.; Actors -- Labor unions -- United States.; Minutes (administrative records); Manuscripts; Legal documents.; Correspondence.; Clippings files.; New York (N.Y.).; Los Angeles (Calif.); Motion picture industry |x Political aspects |z United States; Communism and motion pictures -- United States.; Television broadcasting -- Employees -- Labor unions -- United States; Television journalists.; American Guild of Musical Artists; Associated Actors and Artistes of America; Screen Actors Guild; AFL-CIO; American Arbitration Association; American Federation of Radio Artists; Wolff, Sanford I. "Bud"; Lewis, Irving; Dowell, Reginald; Actors' Equity Association; Television Authority (TVA); Heller, George, 1906-; Groot, Kenneth; American Federation of Television and Radio Artists
- Series I: Minutes
  Arrangement
  The minutes are arranged chronologically.
  Scope and Content Note
  This series is comprised of the minutes of the board of the New York Local, and the transcibed membership meeting minutes of AFRA, AFTRA, and the Television Authority (TVA), which include appeals by members during the blacklist era. The series includes both minutes and full transcriptions of select meetings.
  - Board Meetings, Jan 1951 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Board Meetings, Feb 1951 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Board Meetings, Mar 1951 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Board Meetings, Apr 1951 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Board Meetings, May 1951 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Board Meetings, Jun 1951 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Board Meetings, Sep 1951 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Board Meetings, Oct 1951 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Board Meetings, Nov 1951 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Board Meetings, Dec 1951 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Board Meetings, Jan 1952 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Board Meetings, Feb 1952 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Board Meetings, Mar 1952 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Board Meetings, Apr 1952 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Board Meetings, May 1952 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Board Meetings, Jun 1952 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Board Meetings, Jul 1952 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Board Meetings, Aug 1952 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Board Meetings, Sep 1952 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Board Meetings, Oct 1952 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Board Meetings, Nov 1952 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Board Meetings, Dec 1952 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Board Meetings, Jan 1953 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Board Meetings, Feb 1953 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Board Meetings, Mar 1953 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Board Meetings, Apr 1953 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Board Meetings, May 1953 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Board Meetings, Jun 1953 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Board Meetings, Aug 1953 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Board Meetings, Sep 1953 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Board Meetings, Oct 1953 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Board Meetings, Nov 1953 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Board Meetings, Dec 1953 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Board Meetings, Jan 1954 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Board Meetings, Feb 1954 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Board Meetings, Mar 1954 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Board Meetings, Apr 1954 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Board Meetings, May 1954 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Board Meetings, Jul 1954 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Board Meetings, Aug 1954 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Board Meetings, Sep 1954 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Board Meetings, Oct 1954 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Board Meetings, Nov 1954 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Board Meetings, Jan 1955 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Board Meetings, Feb 1955 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Board Meetings, Mar 1955 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Board Meetings, Apr 1955 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Board Meetings, May 1955 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Board Meetings, Jun 1955 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Board Meetings, Jul 1955 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Board Meetings, Aug 1955 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Board Meetings, Sep 1955 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Board Meetings, Oct 1955 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Board Meetings, Nov 1955 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Board Meetings, Dec 1955 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Board Meetings, Jan 1956 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Board Meetings, Feb 1956 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Board Meetings, Mar 1956 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Board Meetings, Apr 1956 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Board Meetings, May 1956 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Board Meetings, Jun 1956 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Board Meetings, Jul 1956 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Board Meetings, Aug 1956 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Board Meetings, Sep 1956 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Board Meetings, Oct 1956 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Board Meetings, Nov 1956 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Board Meetings, Dec 1956 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Board Meetings, Jan 1957 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Board Meetings, Feb 1957 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Board Meetings, Mar 1957 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Board Meetings, Apr 1957 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Board Meetings, May 1957 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Board Meetings, Jun 1957 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Board Meetings, Jul 1957 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Board Meetings, Aug 1957 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Board Meetings, Sep 1957 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Board Meetings, Oct 1957 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Board Meetings, Nov 25, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Board Meetings, Dec 1957 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Board Meetings, Jan 1958 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Board Meetings, Feb 1958 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Board Meetings, Mar 1958 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Board Meetings, Apr 1958 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Board Meetings, May 1958 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Board Meetings, Jun 1958 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Board Meetings, Jul 1958 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Board Meetings, Aug 1958 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Board Meetings, Sep 1958 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Board Meetings, Oct 1958 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Board Meetings, Nov 1958 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Board Meetings, Dec 1958 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Board Meetings, Jan 1959 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Board Meetings, Feb 1959 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Board Meetings, Mar 1959 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - Board Meetings, Apr 1959 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Board Meetings, May 1959 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Board Meetings, Jun 1959 (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Board Meetings, Jul 1959 (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Board Meetings, Aug 1959 (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Board Meetings, Sep 1959 (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Board Meetings, Oct 1959 (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Board Meetings, Nov 1959 (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Board Meetings, Dec 1959 (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - Board Meetings, Jan 1960 (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Board Meetings, Feb 1960 (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Board Meetings, Mar 1960 (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - Board Meetings, Apr 1960 (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - Board Meetings, May 1960 (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - Board Meetings, Jun 1960 (Box 1, Folder 109)
  - Board Meetings, Jul 1960 (Box 1, Folder 110)
  - Board Meetings, Aug 1960 (Box 1, Folder 111)
  - Board Meetings, Sep 1960 (Box 1, Folder 112)
  - Board Meetings, Oct 1960 (Box 1, Folder 113)
  - Board Meetings, Dec 1960 (Box 1, Folder 114)
  - Board Meetings, Feb 1961 (Box 1, Folder 115)
  - Board Meetings, Mar 1961 (Box 1, Folder 115A)
  - Board Meetings, Apr 1961 (Box 1, Folder 116)
  - Board Meetings, May 1961 (Box 1, Folder 117)
  - Board Meetings, Jun 1961 (Box 1, Folder 118)
  - Board Meetings, Jul 1961 (Box 1, Folder 119)
  - Board Meetings, Aug 1961 (Box 1, Folder 120)
  - Board Meetings, Sep 1961 (Box 1, Folder 121)
  - Board Meetings, Oct 1961 (Box 1, Folder 122)
  - Board Meetings, Nov 1961 (Box 1, Folder 123)
  - Board Meetings, Dec 1961 (Box 1, Folder 124)
  - Board Meetings, Jan 1962 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Board Meetings, Feb 1962 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Board Meetings, Mar 1962 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Board Meetings, Apr 1962 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Board Meetings, May 1962 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Board Meetings, Jun 1962 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Board Meetings, Jul 1962 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Board Meetings, Sep 1962 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Board Meetings, Oct 1962 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Board Meetings, Dec 1962 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Board Meetings, Jan 1963 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Board Meetings, Feb 1963 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Board Meetings, Mar 1963 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Board Meetings, Apr 1963 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Board Meetings, May 1963 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Board Meetings, Jun 1963 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Board Meetings, Jul 1963 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Board Meetings, Sep 1963 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Board Meetings, Oct 1963 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Board Meetings, Nov 1963 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Board Meetings, Dec 1963 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Board Meetings, Jan 1964 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Board Meetings, Feb 1964 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Board Meetings, Mar 1964 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Board Meetings, Apr 1964 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Board Meetings, May 1964 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Board Meetings, Jun 1964 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Board Meetings, Sep 1964 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Board Meetings, Oct 1964 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Board Meetings, Nov 1964 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Board Meetings, Dec 1964 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Board Meetings, Jan 1965 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Board Meetings, Mar 1965 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Board Meetings, Apr 1965 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Board Meetings, May 1965 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Board Meetings, Jun 1965 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Board Meetings, Jul 1965 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Board Meetings, Sep 1965 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Board Meetings, Oct 1965 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Board Meetings, Nov 1965 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Board Meetings, Dec 1965 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Board Meetings, Jan 1966 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Board Meetings, Feb 1966 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Board Meetings, Mar 1966 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Board Meetings, Apr 1966 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Board Meetings, May 1966 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Board Meetings, Jun 1966 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Board Meetings, Jul 1966 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Board Meetings, Sep 1966 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Board Meetings, Oct 1966 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Board Meetings, Nov 1966 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Board Meetings, Dec 1966 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Board Meetings, Jan 1967 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Board Meetings, Jan 1968 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Board Meetings, Feb 1968 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Board Meetings, Mar 1968 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Board Meetings, Apr 1968 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Board Meetings, May 1968 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Board Meetings, Jun 1968 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Board Meetings, Jul 1968 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Board Meetings, Sep 1968 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Board Meetings, Oct 1968 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Board Meetings, Nov 1968 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Board Meetings, Dec 1968 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Board Meetings, Jan 1969 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Board Meetings, Feb 1969 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Board Meetings, Mar 1969 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Board Meetings, Apr 1969 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Board Meetings, May 1969 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Board Meetings, Jun 1969 (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Board Meetings, Jul 1969 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Board Meetings, Sep 1969 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Board Meetings, Oct 1969 (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Board Meetings, Nov 1969 (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Board Meetings, Dec 1969 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Board Meetings, Nov 1970 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Board Meetings, Jan 1971 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Board Meetings, Feb 1971 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Board Meetings, Mar 1971 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Board Meetings, Apr 1971 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Board Meetings, May 1971 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Board Meetings, Jun 1971 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Board Meetings, Sep 1971 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Board Meetings, Oct 1971 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Board Meetings, Nov 1971 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Board Meetings, Dec 1971 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Board Meetings, Jan 1972 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Board Meetings, Feb 1972 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Board Meetings, Mar 1972 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Board Meetings, Apr 1972 (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - Board Meetings, May 1972 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - Board Meetings, Jun 1972 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Board Meetings, Sep 1972 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Board Meetings, Oct 1972 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Board Meetings, Nov 1972 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Board Meetings, Dec 1972 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Board Meetings, Jan 1973 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Board Meetings, Feb 1973 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Board Meetings, Mar 1973 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Board Meetings, Apr 1973 (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Board Meetings, May 1973 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Board Meetings, Jun 1973 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Board Meetings, Aug 1973 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Board Meetings, Oct 1973 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Board Meetings, Nov 1973 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Board Meetings, Dec 1973 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Board Meetings, Jan 1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Board Meetings, Feb 1974 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Board Meetings, Mar 1974 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Board Meetings, Apr 1974 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Board Meetings, May 1974 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Board Meetings, Jun 1974 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Board Meetings, Jul 1974 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Board Meetings, Aug 1974 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Board Meetings, Oct 1974 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Board Meetings, Nov 1974 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Board Meetings, Dec 1974 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Board Meetings, Jan 1975 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Board Meetings, Feb 1975 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Board Meetings, Mar 1975 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Board Meetings, Apr 1975 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Board Meetings, May 1975 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Board Meetings, Jun 1975 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Board Meetings, Aug 1975 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Board Meetings, Sep 1975 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Board Meetings, Oct 1975 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Board Meetings, Dec 1975 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Board Meetings, Jan 1976 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Board Meetings, Feb 1976 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Board Meetings, Mar 1976 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Board Meetings, Apr 1976 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Board Meetings, Jun 1976 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Board Meetings, Sep 1976 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Board Meetings, Oct 1976 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Board Meetings, Nov 1976 (Box 3, Folder 35)